It has begun! Hachamacha Gakuen!
Yay!
We, the members of Shachi
Nagoya information, the mysteries of the Tokai region
We will discover and transmit information about Nagoya, the mysteries of the Tokai region, and the deepest aspects of the region's history.
We will discover and transmit to everyone!
We call it "Dive into Deep Nagoya"!
This time, we'll dive into the Nishi Ward of Nagoya City.
This time we are in Meido-cho, Nishi-ku, Nagoya City!
Thank you very much!
If you gave me this paper, it means you are on a mission!
I'll be there as soon as I can!
Dalang!
BOS
Sneak into a candy shop in Nagoya!
Is it okay?
I love candy shops!
I like all the members, but probably my favorite!
Mmmmmmmm...
So let's see if there's one nearby!
Let's go there!
Nagoya's candy shop
Tong shop means that they sell a lot of different things.
means they sell a lot of different kinds of things!
I can already see it.
Is that it?
That one!
Mmmmmm...
Mmm-hmm.
Ta-da!
Ta-da! Sakurai Sakurai Shoten, the bagged confectionery specialty store!
They sell a lot of different kinds of confections!
Let's hear what they have to say!
Hello!
Welcome!
Please come in!
I am Haruna Sakamoto from Team Shachi. I look forward to working with you!
Welcome!
It's amazing! The amount of sweets!
Yes!
How many kinds of sweets do you actually have?
1000 kinds, and more!
A thousand kinds? More?
More, I bet!
Wow!
May I take a look now?
Yes, please!
I loved it!
Hey, hey, hey, hey!
Wow!
This brown stuff! I loved it so much!
Kalume-yaki, right?
I used to eat these and the ones with the sticks!
And these cute little ones too!
What? This is the one in the fruit forest, right?
Yes, yes, yes!
Beautiful!
You can use the grabbing ones for that!
These are the ones in the fruit forest!
The sticky ones!
I miss those!
Wow!
I was born in Nagoya!
Wow! That's amazing!
I like candy too, and I eat a lot of it.
If you look at the back, you can see Nagoya city, or Tokai region, or Nishi ward in particular.
Especially in Nishi Ward!
Nishi Ward?
Nishi Ward!
This one too!
This is Nishi Ward too!
I always put Sakurombo and Shochu in the candy store!
That's right!
This one too!
Yes, yes!
Mocchan dango! I miss them!
These are all in Nishi Ward!
Wow!
This is Nishi Ward too!
That's amazing!
Like the tons of shops, candy shops, and rice cake shops.
There are a lot of them in this area, aren't there?
So many!
There were about 100 shops!
Wow! Is that so?
Why are there so many? In this area!
Since the Edo period, when Nagoya Castle was built, they used to offer sweets to the castle builders.
Craftsmen gathered nearby, and confectionary making flourished.
That's right!I see!
So this is how you actually buy boxes and stuff?
Basically, yes!
But when little kids come, I tell them that I have roses here, too.
This is very popular with the kids.
League! League gum?
There's a league.
Sounds fun! It's a game!
Yes, yes, yes! That's how you do it.
You push and it comes out!
How do you like them? Tits!
Ah! Chocolate tits!
I miss the boob chocolates!
No, this is for adults!
This is Nagoya's famous wedding candy!
It's a set! Look at this!
Is this Nagoya's wedding candy?
Yes, they are! This is the Nagoya custom!
Here's one from my wedding.
Oh, wow! Are you going to show me something so beautiful?
Wrapped in roses!
Kashimaki?
Yes, yes! And then it becomes a bag like this.
That's right!
We started to give them out to our neighbors.
It's true that Nagoya has a custom of kashimaki.
Nagoya's sweets sell well no matter where you take them, whether Tokyo or Osaka
Nagoya sweets sell well no matter where you take them!
That's right!
When the Great Kanto Earthquake hit, we delivered sweets from Nagoya
We became famous again!
Oh, I see!
I'm going to look for my favorite sweets
I'll get some and buy some too!
Maybe I'll try the fugashi.
But a big batch of Umaibo is good too!
A lot of Umaibo is good too!
I'll try to get a big bag of Umaibo too.
These are Umaibo too!
Yea!
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
This is...
I see these every once in a while.
You see it?
In arcade games.
They have them in arcades, don't they?
That's right.
They have all kinds of flavors.
It comes in many flavors.
Yes, they do.
Okay, then.
What should I make?
I'm going to go ahead and try it.
A big bag full of them.
Can I buy one?
Fugashika
Umaibo
can
Wow!
There's so many in here!
Yes, it is!
Our original
Original
That's amazing!
There's natto in it too!
Yes, it is.
That's amazing!
Ah!
And his favorite cod roe.
And chocolate.
There's chocolate in it, too.
Oh, really?
Oh...
I think I'll have this one.
This one.
This one, please.
Yes, please.
Okay?
Yay!
Wow, that's a first for a Z.
But you're not?
And it's tonight.
What are we gonna do?
What am I gonna buy?
Oh, look what I found!
Chocolate hearts!
And with a message. It says it's a chocolate with a sincere message.
I guess we should eat this together as a token of our appreciation.
Give me 520 yen.
Cut! Thank you very much.Cut! Thank you very much.
Wow, Meido-cho.
Even after walking from the candy store earlier, there are so many interesting stores.
Look at them!
If you see it, you have no choice but to enter.
Let's go in. It looks interesting.
Wow. Excuse me.
Good night.
Hello. Welcome.
Hello.
Hello. It's nice to meet you. I am Haruna Sakamoto from Team Shashi. I am Haruna Sakamoto of Team Shashi.
My name is Hori from Hori Shoten.
Are you Hori from Hori Shoten?
I am Hori.
What kind of store are you going to be?
We have a wide range of products that children enjoy,
We have toys, stationery, general merchandise, and other items that are used for events and presentations.
We have a wide range of products that make children happy.
Our customers are people who want to make children happy.
Wow, that's amazing. A lot of children's dreams.
That's an original candy lift, isn't it?
You also have candy.
We are more than a candy store selling candy in bulk,
We are good at making our own original and cute packages.
That's great. My sister had a baby the year before last, I think. She was born the year before last and is now about two years old,
She has recently been looking at toys that she has not been exposed to as an adult.
I understand.
I think it would be a lot of fun to come with your child.
Really? I want to bring them.
Oh, a fair. A fair is a festival, right?
Yes, it is. We also have people who want to hold their own festivals,
And we have products that look like they are actually sold at the street stalls.
That's amazing. Po-ii. Po-i, right? It's Poi, isn't it?
It's Po-oi.
That's great. Maybe that's what it means. Or, it's a noodle.
We also sell noodles.
Oh, wow.
A super ball.
May I hold it?
Please hold it.
It looks really heavy.
It is heavy.
When I came over here, I was asked to bring a basket of toys to give away as prizes for children's lunches.
There are a lot of toys for children to choose from.
Like this miniature car. I'm sure the kids would love it.
We also sell toys that you can play with.
Oh, they sell toys like gakacha-gakacha.
They also sell the machine itself.
That's amazing. You can buy one when you grow up.
You can play with it at home.
I wish I could bring my son along.
But I really feel like my little boy is going to go "boo boo" when he sees a car right now.
I wondered if he would notice how great it is since he says "boo-boo" when he sees a car.
I hope he does.
If you go to the second floor, you can find toys such as radio-controlled toys and a wide range of stationery.
Would you like to go upstairs?
May I take a look?
Bb-bb-boo!
Boys love working cars more than sports cars, don't they?
They call them police cars and fire trucks.
I want to buy them all. No, I can't.
Up there is a big jeep radio-controlled on the right hand side.
This way? Cool!
I think this is exciting even for adults.
It's more like an adult's kind of thing.
No doubt about it.
It's so cool! I love it.
These days, helicopters, drones, and other things that weren't toys a decade ago are being sold as toys.
This is a drone, right?
A drone of this size is amazing!
It has a propeller inside and the ball floats in the palm of your hand.
What's that? Amazing!
It's a bit futuristic.
I don't think they had them when I was little. Like when I was in elementary school.
Toys are evolving rapidly, aren't they?
Oh! Wait, wait, wait!
That's great! Over here! I was just looking at it thinking, "Wow, it's got my name on it!
I put it in.
Thank you!
Welcome.
Nao was with us just now, too.
Hey! Thank you! Surprise!
It's a gift for a birthday party, a piano recital, a store opening, etc. It can be delivered all over the country.
It has a bunch of sweets on it.
You can pull them out one by one.
So you can take them home with you, just like the flowers?
Yes, that's right.
That's amazing!
You can share it with everyone.
If you send them to a birthday party next year or something like that, you can ask your customers to take them home with them. That's the kind of store I'm talking about.
I love this!I love this so much!!!
This was also thought up, wasn't it?
This was also created by sharing ideas with other companies.
Amazing! Like the assortment of sweets over there that I mentioned at the beginning, you are a man of ideas, aren't you?
Everyone in the company came up with the idea together.
Everyone is amazing. So many fun things to do.
It was a lot of fun!
I guess it's because I'm an adult that I'm able to buy a lot of things at a ton of stores.
You can buy a larger quantity of things, you know.
And there's the fun of choosing what to buy.
If I had come here when I was a little kid, it would have been a dream world, wouldn't it?
It was so wonderful!
Next time, I'd like to bring my children with me!
Hey, hey, hey!
Please take a souvenir from us!
Wow!
A treasure box?
It's a treasure chest! Wow!
Here you go.
Thank you very much.
Open it.
What's this? I've never received a treasure chest before.
Wow!
Oh, no, no, no, no, no!
Carrots!
Bon appétit, everyone.
Are you sure? You sure?
Yay! Thank you so much!
And I'll put some glow-in-the-dark candy on it.
Yay! I'll take the glowing candy.
They glow and you can eat them.
Really?
I get them at a candy store in Japan, so they taste really good.
It's amazing!
You can even make your own colors and shapes.
Is that so?
I hope to have a chance someday.
Thank you very much!
I received this from Saori Hori, the treasure box store.
I'm sure the members will love it, and I'm sure I'll be back to visit with them again.
I'll definitely come visit you.
Please come visit us! Thank you very much!
Please come and visit us too!
We got a treasure chest!
It's time for Orca News.
It's that time already.
Let's have a sip.
In the meantime, I have something for you.
On March 1, we launched a new product.
We, Team Killer Whale, and Coming Flavor-chan have collaborated to release a new song.
Yay! It's Shachifre.
It's one of the songs from Eyes Fried and Super Walpurgis.
Both of them are totally different songs.
We've already performed them last time, but we're going to pull this single down for events, developments, and various other things,
Please check back often.
You can listen to the two songs that we sing as Orca Frei on the soundtrack,
We also have our own shachi versions of "Eyes Fried" and "Super Walpurgis",
Please look forward to it.
We are nervous too.
It might sound a little different, and we would like to perform it live as well.
But I think this is the best time to listen to them as Shachifre,
We are looking forward to hearing from you.
We look forward to hearing from you.
That was the orca news.